1
00:00:01,170 --> 00:00:03,150
"闪电侠" "超女"前情回顾
Previously on "The Flash" and "Supergirl"...

2
00:00:03,180 --> 00:00:04,420
他怎么了
What just happened to him?

3
00:00:04,440 --> 00:00:07,370
沃利就在神速力接我的班
Wally has taken my place in the Speed Force.

4
00:00:07,390 --> 00:00:09,490
没事了 我们回家了
It's okay, we're going home.

5
00:00:09,500 --> 00:00:11,810
沃利看到的 够他好受一阵了
What Wally saw, it's gonna haunt him for a while.

6
00:00:11,830 --> 00:00:15,330
我以为向你求婚就可以救你
I proposed because I thought it would save you.

7
00:00:15,360 --> 00:00:18,380
-什么意思  -我觉得我们要分开一段时间
- What does that mean? - I think we need some space.

8
00:00:18,410 --> 00:00:20,110
我欠你一个真相 我叫蒙-艾尔
I owe you the truth. My name is Mon-El.

9
00:00:20,130 --> 00:00:21,480
达星以前的王子
I'm the former Prince of Daxam.

10
00:00:21,510 --> 00:00:23,690
我不应该被人蒙在鼓里
I deserve better than being lied to.

11
00:00:23,720 --> 00:00:25,010
我一直在找你
I've been looking for you.

12
00:00:29,480 --> 00:00:31,330
再见
Toodles!

13
00:00:37,340 --> 00:00:38,560
我就说
I told you.

14
00:00:38,580 --> 00:00:40,240
歌声往往更动听
Everything's better in song.

15
00:00:40,250 --> 00:00:42,650
简单的几个词语
When you speak, it's just words.

16
00:00:42,650 --> 00:00:44,990
歌唱时却能让你放飞灵魂
But when you sing, you open up your soul

17
00:00:45,010 --> 00:00:47,380
展现你自己独一无二的闪光点
and let who you really are shine through.

18
00:00:47,390 --> 00:00:48,520
谢谢你 妈妈
Thanks, Mom.

19
00:00:48,550 --> 00:00:50,750
我爱你 宝贝儿子
Hmm. I love you, my beautiful boy.

20
00:00:50,760 --> 00:00:52,960
我也爱你
I love you too.

21
00:00:52,980 --> 00:00:56,520
♪ 我又重获笑颜 ♪ 
♪ I'm happy again ♪

22
00:00:56,700 --> 00:00:59,260
♪ 我嘲笑那乌云 ♪ 
♪ I'm laughing at clouds ♪

23
00:00:59,260 --> 00:01:02,430
♪ 如此阴暗遮住天空 ♪
♪ So dark up above ♪

24
00:01:02,430 --> 00:01:04,010
这...
This...

25
00:01:04,040 --> 00:01:05,600
又看《雨中曲》
again?

26
00:01:06,300 --> 00:01:08,000
你是打算在沙发里
What, are you gonna spend the rest of your life

27
00:01:08,020 --> 00:01:09,310
窝一辈子吗 快起来
sitting around on the couch? Come on.

28
00:01:09,330 --> 00:01:11,200
你已经看了好几天了 起来嗨
You've been doing this for days. Let's do something.

29
00:01:11,220 --> 00:01:12,660
-出去逛逛吧  -不要 我不去
- Let's go out. - No, man, I'm sorry.

30
00:01:12,660 --> 00:01:13,950
我... 我不想出去
I... I don't feel like going out.

31
00:01:13,980 --> 00:01:16,920
你这几天看音乐剧入迷啦
What is it with you and musicals these days anyhow?

32
00:01:16,940 --> 00:01:19,110
歌声往往更动听
Everything's better in song.

33
00:01:20,000 --> 00:01:21,300
听我说
Listen, dude,

34
00:01:21,330 --> 00:01:22,760
我知道 爱瑞斯解除婚约
I know you've been going through a tough time

35
00:01:22,790 --> 00:01:25,280
你现在心里正难受
since Iris broke off the engagement,

36
00:01:25,300 --> 00:01:26,640
-应该说...  -什么
- or, I guess... - What?

37
00:01:26,660 --> 00:01:28,440
... 严格来说 是你解除婚约
... technically, since you broke off the engagement.

38
00:01:28,470 --> 00:01:30,100
总之不管谁解除的
Whoever broke off the engagement,

39
00:01:30,130 --> 00:01:31,690
都一样 我只是...
it doesn't matter, I just...

40
00:01:31,700 --> 00:01:33,330
我只是想帮你
I don't know, man. I want to help.

41
00:01:33,330 --> 00:01:34,860
你其实帮不到我
Nothing you can really do.

42
00:01:34,870 --> 00:01:37,090
真的吗 那我只好让...
Really? I guess I'm just gonna have to let...

43
00:01:37,120 --> 00:01:39,040
吉恩·凯利先生[好莱坞歌舞片巨星]来了
Mr. Gene Kelly take over

44
00:01:39,040 --> 00:01:41,640
谁知道呢 我啥也做不了不是 
'cause, Lord knows, I can't do anything about that.

45
00:01:45,880 --> 00:01:48,430
-是小哈  -我也收到了
- It's H.R. - Yeah.

46
00:01:56,890 --> 00:01:58,530
小巴
B.A.,

47
00:01:58,550 --> 00:02:00,290
有朋自远方来
someone's coming through.

48
00:02:00,290 --> 00:02:02,150
可能是吉普赛
Could be Gypsy.

49
00:02:02,660 --> 00:02:04,390
有可能 也许是...
Could be, or it could be...

50
00:02:07,190 --> 00:02:09,150
超女
Supergirl?

51
00:02:09,530 --> 00:02:10,790
卡拉...
Kara...

52
00:02:11,970 --> 00:02:14,160
-她怎么了  -我们也不知道
- What happened to her? - We don't know,

53
00:02:14,190 --> 00:02:17,050
但始作俑者也来到这个星球了
but whoever did it has come to this world.

54
00:02:24,310 --> 00:02:25,650
生命体征微弱
Her vitals are low.

55
00:02:25,650 --> 00:02:27,120
她昏厥多久了
How long has she been like this?

56
00:02:27,120 --> 00:02:29,160
几个小时
A few hours.

57
00:02:29,720 --> 00:02:32,220
我们一定要找到罪魁祸首
Okay, we need to find whoever did this to Kara

58
00:02:32,240 --> 00:02:34,360
一顿暴走 直到他跪地求饶
and punch him repeatedly until he reverses

59
00:02:34,360 --> 00:02:35,750
收回咒语 唤醒卡拉
whatever spell he put on her,

60
00:02:35,780 --> 00:02:37,040
而且我要第一个揍他
and I get to punch him first.

61
00:02:37,070 --> 00:02:38,430
你到底是谁
Who are you exactly?

62
00:02:38,430 --> 00:02:39,930
我叫蒙-艾尔
My name is Mon-El.

63
00:02:39,930 --> 00:02:41,630
我是... 我是卡拉的...
I'm... I'm Kara's...

64
00:02:41,630 --> 00:02:43,250
朋友
friend.

65
00:02:43,420 --> 00:02:46,010
我们... 友达以上
We're more... more than friend.

66
00:02:47,120 --> 00:02:48,520
时不时亲个小嘴儿
We've been kissing a lot.

67
00:02:48,550 --> 00:02:50,760
她可没说自己有个男朋友
Oh, she never mentioned she had a boyfriend.

68
00:02:50,790 --> 00:02:52,790
最近的事儿 所以...
It's a recent thing, so...

69
00:02:52,810 --> 00:02:54,880
你俩不是分手了吗
I thought you two broke up.

70
00:02:56,340 --> 00:02:58,010
我插一句 尽量别提分手俩字
I tell you what, I know enough not to mention

71
00:02:58,020 --> 00:03:00,510
尤其当着巴里和... 那谁...
the break-up between Barry and... uh...

72
00:03:00,920 --> 00:03:02,490
-小哈  -对不起
- H.R. - Sorry.

73
00:03:03,710 --> 00:03:06,110
不管我跟卡拉之间发生了什么
Look, hey, whatever's going on between me and Kara,

74
00:03:06,130 --> 00:03:08,060
我也不能让她不省人事
I cannot leave her like this, okay?

75
00:03:08,060 --> 00:03:10,440
-我要救她  -我们会救她的 我保证
- I need to get her back. - We will, I promise.

76
00:03:11,520 --> 00:03:13,320
所以她到底怎么了
So what happened to her?

77
00:03:13,340 --> 00:03:15,190
一名外星囚犯逃出监守所
An alien prisoner escaped our custody.

78
00:03:15,220 --> 00:03:17,550
不知道耍了什么把戏 让卡拉晕厥
He did something to her, put her in some kind of a coma.

79
00:03:17,550 --> 00:03:18,850
然后就消失了
And then he disappeared.

80
00:03:18,860 --> 00:03:20,320
我们一路跟踪他到这
We tracked him here and followed.

81
00:03:20,320 --> 00:03:22,170
他为什么来这里
Okay, but why would he come to this Earth?

82
00:03:22,190 --> 00:03:24,740
我们觉得... 是冲你来的
Well, we believe... for you.

83
00:03:24,760 --> 00:03:26,490
-我吗 为什么  -不知道
- Me? Why? - We don't know.

84
00:03:26,500 --> 00:03:28,080
可他走前撂了一句
But his last words before he disappeared

85
00:03:28,100 --> 00:03:30,750
说要去找速度最快的人
were about finding the fastest man alive.

86
00:03:31,830 --> 00:03:34,790
当务之急就是要把这时空穿梭者抓出来
Okay, well, clearly, we're talking about a breacher here.

87
00:03:34,820 --> 00:03:36,800
我唯一擅长的
And if there's one thing I can do,

88
00:03:36,830 --> 00:03:38,540
也就找穿梭者了
it's find breachers.

89
00:03:42,280 --> 00:03:44,490
还有什么细节吗
So what else can you tell us about this guy?

90
00:03:44,510 --> 00:03:45,720
不是很多
Not much.

91
00:03:45,740 --> 00:03:47,960
他来去无踪
It's like he just materialized out of thin air.

92
00:03:47,970 --> 00:03:50,320
你说的是他吗
You mean like this clown just did?

93
00:03:53,630 --> 00:03:54,870
我去
I'm gonna go.

94
00:03:59,380 --> 00:04:00,890
华莱士...
Wallace...

95
00:04:01,890 --> 00:04:03,680
我知道你现在也不好受
I understand what you've been through.

96
00:04:03,680 --> 00:04:06,570
困在神速力里 不断经历痛苦... 我能理解
Stuck in the Speed Force, things you saw... I get it.

97
00:04:06,590 --> 00:04:09,470
我也知道俗话说得好
I also know that sometimes, the old adage is true.

98
00:04:09,490 --> 00:04:10,920
你摔下马时
When you get bucked from the horse,

99
00:04:10,920 --> 00:04:12,690
唯一能做的...
best thing you can do...

100
00:04:12,690 --> 00:04:14,520
就是爬上去
get right back on the damn thing

101
00:04:14,520 --> 00:04:16,290
征服它 华莱士
and ride, Wallace.

102
00:04:16,290 --> 00:04:17,690
征服
Ride!

103
00:04:23,800 --> 00:04:26,000
你好啊 巴里·艾伦
Hello, Barry Allen.

104
00:04:26,160 --> 00:04:27,890
-你是怎么...  -知道你名字吗
- How do you... - Know your name?

105
00:04:27,920 --> 00:04:29,770
我知道的多了去了
I know a lot of things.

106
00:04:29,770 --> 00:04:32,270
而且我无所不能哦
And I can do a lot of things too.

107
00:04:33,910 --> 00:04:35,560
沃利·韦斯特也来了啊
Wally West made it here too.

108
00:04:35,580 --> 00:04:37,010
真激动人心
This is exciting.

109
00:04:37,010 --> 00:04:38,810
欢迎你也来参加这次派对 闪电小子
It's good of you to join the party, Kid Flash.

110
00:04:38,820 --> 00:04:40,210
热烈欢迎你
I'm happy to have you.

111
00:04:40,240 --> 00:04:41,520
你对超女做了什么
What do you want with Supergirl?

112
00:04:41,520 --> 00:04:44,170
马上就知道了
Same thing that I want with both of you.

113
00:04:44,600 --> 00:04:46,480
给你们上一课
To teach you all a lesson.

114
00:04:53,530 --> 00:04:54,930
你就这点能耐吗 闪电小子
Is that all you got, Kid Flash?

115
00:04:54,930 --> 00:04:57,550
看起来有点紧张啊
I mean, you look a little scared.

116
00:04:59,790 --> 00:05:01,600
你太慢了
And you're too slow.

117
00:05:04,960 --> 00:05:06,610
晚安 闪电侠
Nighty-night, Flash.

118
00:05:26,030 --> 00:05:28,840
-♪ 月亮... ♪  -什么鬼
- ♪ Moon... ♪ - What the hell?

119
00:05:28,870 --> 00:05:31,220
♪ 河 ♪ 
♪ River ♪

120
00:05:31,670 --> 00:05:36,400
♪ 绚丽水镜铺满千里 ♪ 
♪ Wider than a mile ♪

121
00:05:36,410 --> 00:05:38,670
♪ 也许有天... ♪ 
♪ I'm crossing... ♪

122
00:05:38,680 --> 00:05:39,840
卡拉
Kara?

123
00:05:39,870 --> 00:05:44,890
♪ 我将遇见你 ♪ 
♪ You in style someday ♪

124
00:05:47,270 --> 00:05:52,770
♪ 织梦的河啊 ♪ 
♪ Oh, dream maker ♪

125
00:05:53,060 --> 00:05:57,820
♪ 碎梦的河啊 ♪ 
♪ You heart breaker ♪

126
00:05:58,500 --> 00:06:03,820
♪ 不论你流向何方 ♪ 
♪ Wherever you're going ♪

127
00:06:03,980 --> 00:06:06,510
♪ 我都会 ♪ 
♪ I'm going... ♪

128
00:06:06,540 --> 00:06:11,320
♪ 随你而去 ♪ 
♪ Your way ♪

129
00:06:12,890 --> 00:06:17,940
♪ 共同漂泊 ♪ 
♪ Two drifters ♪

130
00:06:18,420 --> 00:06:22,970
♪ 欣赏大千世界 ♪ 
♪ Off to see the world ♪

131
00:06:23,660 --> 00:06:28,550
♪ 世界的精彩绚烂 ♪ 
♪ There's such a lot of world ♪

132
00:06:28,570 --> 00:06:33,660
♪ 等着我们去发现 ♪ 
♪ To see ♪

133
00:06:33,850 --> 00:06:39,470
♪ 我们追逐 ♪ 
♪ We're after ♪

134
00:06:39,470 --> 00:06:42,890
♪ 同一道... ♪ 
♪ The same... ♪

135
00:06:42,910 --> 00:06:48,150
♪ 彩虹的尽头 ♪ 
♪ Rainbow's end ♪

136
00:06:49,450 --> 00:06:53,710
♪ 静静在弧线上等待 ♪ 
♪ Waiting 'round the bend ♪

137
00:06:54,690 --> 00:06:59,360
♪ 那有我可爱的朋友 ♪ 
♪ My huckleberry friend ♪

138
00:06:59,830 --> 00:07:05,120
♪ 月亮河 ♪ 
♪ Moon river ♪

139
00:07:07,340 --> 00:07:11,700
♪ 与我... ♪ 
♪ And me... ♪

140
00:07:18,780 --> 00:07:20,450
唱得真棒
What a singer, huh?

141
00:07:20,470 --> 00:07:22,140
-对  -你认识她吗
- Yeah. - You know her?

142
00:07:22,160 --> 00:07:24,030
对 我认识
Yeah, I do.

143
00:07:27,610 --> 00:07:28,770
女士们先生们...
Ladies and gentlemen...

144
00:07:28,800 --> 00:07:30,060
-巴里  -嘿
- Barry? - Hey!

145
00:07:30,070 --> 00:07:32,480
巴里 真的是你 感谢上帝
Barry! It's you, thank Rao!

146
00:07:32,690 --> 00:07:34,340
等等 真是你吧
Oh, wait, it's really you, right?

147
00:07:34,370 --> 00:07:35,850
-对 是我  -很好
- Yeah, this is me, yeah. - Good.

148
00:07:35,870 --> 00:07:38,100
我们到底在哪 发生什么了
What is... where the hell are we? What's going on?

149
00:07:38,120 --> 00:07:39,810
我还想问你来着
I was hoping you could tell me

150
00:07:39,840 --> 00:07:42,140
为什么我穿得跟奥黛丽赫本一样
or maybe explain to me why I just pulled an Audrey Hepburn

151
00:07:42,160 --> 00:07:43,930
在夜店唱歌呢
and sang in a nightclub.

152
00:07:43,950 --> 00:07:46,080
-咱俩是在做梦吗  -还是同一个梦
- Maybe we're dreaming? - The same dream?

153
00:07:46,100 --> 00:07:47,780
对 真是... 在你来这之前
Yeah, that's... What's the last thing you remember

154
00:07:47,800 --> 00:07:48,830
做的最后一件事是什么
before you got here?

155
00:07:48,860 --> 00:07:50,530
我在超常行动部
I was at the D.E.O.

156
00:07:50,550 --> 00:07:52,420
他们带来一名外星囚犯
They had just brought in an alien prisoner.

157
00:07:52,420 --> 00:07:54,520
他逃了 然后...
He got loose, and...

158
00:07:54,570 --> 00:07:56,810
很奇怪 他有那个红色...
it was really weird. He had this, um, red...

159
00:07:56,840 --> 00:07:58,610
-手帕  -对
- ... Pocket handkerchief? - Yes!

160
00:07:58,640 --> 00:08:00,880
你在我星球上 昏迷不醒
I saw you on my Earth. You were in a coma.

161
00:08:00,910 --> 00:08:02,470
你男朋友带你来找我们
Your boyfriend brought you to us.

162
00:08:02,470 --> 00:08:04,200
他不是我男朋友
He is not my boyfriend.

163
00:08:04,200 --> 00:08:05,970
他... 就是个毛小子
He... he's just a boy.

164
00:08:05,990 --> 00:08:07,030
也不是我朋友
Who is not my friend.

165
00:08:07,050 --> 00:08:09,150
-啥都不是  -好吧
- He's my nothing. - Okay.

166
00:08:09,310 --> 00:08:11,030
不管他是谁
All right, uh, well, whoever he is

167
00:08:11,060 --> 00:08:12,740
他说有人迷晕了你
said that this guy whammied you,

168
00:08:12,770 --> 00:08:14,950
然后逃到我们星球 接着出现在科学之星实验室
and then he escaped to my Earth, he showed up at S.T.A.R. Labs,

169
00:08:14,970 --> 00:08:16,870
我去追他 想让他把你叫醒
I went after him to try to get him to wake you up...

170
00:08:16,890 --> 00:08:18,430
-然后你就被迷晕了  -是的
- And then you got whammied. - Yeah.

171
00:08:18,430 --> 00:08:19,930
-所以我们现在在哪  -我也不知道
- So where are we? - I don't know.

172
00:08:19,930 --> 00:08:22,030
也许是平行时空 或者是...
I mean, it could be a parallel dimension, or...

173
00:08:22,040 --> 00:08:23,740
复杂的幻想
maybe just some elaborate illusion.

174
00:08:23,770 --> 00:08:25,150
我们得想个办法
We just need to figure a way out.

175
00:08:25,170 --> 00:08:28,840
也许脚跟碰三下就行了[绿野仙踪]
I guess I could click my heels together three times.

176
00:08:28,840 --> 00:08:30,740
-有道理  -我开玩笑呢
- Yeah... - I was kidding.

177
00:08:31,050 --> 00:08:33,170
这样啊 好的...
Okay, all right, well...

178
00:08:33,200 --> 00:08:34,780
快来
Come on. Let's...

179
00:08:36,120 --> 00:08:37,580
顺便啰嗦一句 你唱歌真好听
You're a really good singer, by the way.

180
00:08:37,600 --> 00:08:40,750
谢了 我姐姐说我名字就取的卡拉ok前俩字
Hey, thanks. My sister says I put the "Kara" in "karaoke."

181
00:08:40,750 --> 00:08:42,610
你们在这
There you are!

182
00:08:43,150 --> 00:08:44,270
梅林...
Merlyn...

183
00:08:44,290 --> 00:08:45,470
-谁  -你说谁
- Who? - Who?

184
00:08:45,500 --> 00:08:47,670
马尔科姆·梅林 刺客联盟前头领
Malcolm Merlyn. Former head of the League of Assassins.

185
00:08:47,690 --> 00:08:48,960
什么的什么
The what of the what?

186
00:08:48,980 --> 00:08:50,450
你俩臭小子说什么呢
What the hell you talking about, kid?

187
00:08:50,470 --> 00:08:52,260
我叫砍特·莫兰 夜店老板
My name's Cutter Moran, I own this club,

188
00:08:52,290 --> 00:08:53,790
你们俩都是我员工
and both of you work for me.

189
00:08:53,810 --> 00:08:54,930
我们什么
We what now?

190
00:08:54,950 --> 00:08:58,080
我花钱请你唱歌 没让你问问题
I pay you to sing, not pepper me with questions.

191
00:08:58,110 --> 00:08:59,740
我希望你好好选歌
And I hope you got something better in your songbook

192
00:08:59,740 --> 00:09:01,460
而不是在那引吭高歌 金发妞
than what you were belting out up there, blondie.

193
00:09:01,480 --> 00:09:03,270
别叫我金发妞
Hey! Don't call me blondie.

194
00:09:03,280 --> 00:09:04,600
我不知道你是谁...
Hey, look, I don't know who you are...

195
00:09:04,620 --> 00:09:06,020
原来是小刀无影手
obviously you're someone who's quick with a knife.

196
00:09:06,050 --> 00:09:08,680
请原谅我朋友 他说话不过脑
You have to excuse my friend. He doesn't think before he talks.

197
00:09:08,690 --> 00:09:10,120
我侄子也那样
Yeah, I had a cousin like that.

198
00:09:10,120 --> 00:09:11,730
我就割断了他的喉咙
I had to slit his throat too.

199
00:09:12,900 --> 00:09:14,830
格雷迪 让他俩准备一下
Grady! Get these two set up.

200
00:09:14,860 --> 00:09:16,020
我想听点新歌
And nothing I've heard before.

201
00:09:16,030 --> 00:09:18,720
原创歌曲
I want something original.

202
00:09:19,040 --> 00:09:20,780
巴里 我失去超能力了
Barry, I don't have my powers.

203
00:09:20,800 --> 00:09:22,330
我也是
Me neither.

204
00:09:23,610 --> 00:09:24,870
维恩
Winn!

205
00:09:24,890 --> 00:09:26,240
维恩 你也吗
Winn, you're here too?

206
00:09:26,260 --> 00:09:27,670
谁是维恩 我叫格雷迪
Ah! Who's Winn? The name is Grady.

207
00:09:27,670 --> 00:09:29,140
我是弹钢琴的
I tickle the keys around here.

208
00:09:29,140 --> 00:09:31,650
你知道他为什么叫“砍爷”吗
Say, you realize how he got the nickname "Cutter," don't you?

209
00:09:31,670 --> 00:09:33,870
-不知道  -因为他喜欢砍人
- No. - Because he likes to cut people.

210
00:09:35,010 --> 00:09:36,470
还是问我吧 他会一直唠下去
You ask me, I think he's all talk.

211
00:09:36,500 --> 00:09:39,230
西斯科 不是西斯科 你好
Cisco... not Cisco. Hello.

212
00:09:39,230 --> 00:09:41,100
我保证 总有一天
I pray that, one day, you do not find out

213
00:09:41,120 --> 00:09:43,480
你会发现自己大错特错 帕布洛
how very, very wrong you are, Pablo.

214
00:09:43,500 --> 00:09:46,140
-干你的活去吧  -好吧
- Now go do your job. - All right.

215
00:09:47,910 --> 00:09:49,640
格雷迪不知道 不过总有一天
You see, Grady doesn't know this, but one day,

216
00:09:49,660 --> 00:09:51,370
我会出人头地
I'm gonna be somebody.

217
00:09:51,520 --> 00:09:53,020
一定会的 而且就在
I'm gonna be somebody, and it's gonna happen

218
00:09:53,040 --> 00:09:55,080
那舞台上大放光彩
right there on that stage.

219
00:09:55,100 --> 00:09:57,380
等着瞧 只消一个契机
You'll see. I just need my one shot.

220
00:09:58,080 --> 00:10:00,190
真是越来越有趣了
It's just curiouser and curiouser.

221
00:10:00,230 --> 00:10:02,080
是啊 好像"绿野仙踪"
Yeah, yeah, it's like "The Wizard of Oz."

222
00:10:02,110 --> 00:10:03,780
-是的  -"你在这里
- Yeah. - "And you were there,

223
00:10:03,810 --> 00:10:05,660
-"又在那里"  -不过他们不是真的
- "and you were there...." - Except, it's not really them.

224
00:10:05,680 --> 00:10:07,630
他们都是音乐剧里的...
They're all playing characters in a...

225
00:10:07,650 --> 00:10:09,440
... 角色
... Musical.


226
00:10:09,530 --> 00:10:12,310
巴里 我们到底在哪
Barry, where are we?

227
00:10:12,340 --> 00:10:13,870
不知道
I don't know.

228
00:10:13,890 --> 00:10:16,400
要知道人们常说...
Well, you know what they say...

229
00:10:16,810 --> 00:10:19,400
演出还得继续
the show must go on!

230
00:10:20,600 --> 00:10:22,550
超女 我喜欢你唱的"月亮河"
Supergirl, I loved your rendition of "Moon River,"

231
00:10:22,580 --> 00:10:23,720
多美的一首歌
such a beautiful song.

232
00:10:23,740 --> 00:10:24,900
有几处唱得很平淡
You were a little flat in places,

233
00:10:24,930 --> 00:10:27,670
但你在台上太可爱了让我不愿打断
but I'm willing to let it slide just because you're so cute.

234
00:10:27,700 --> 00:10:30,280
-等等 你对我们干了什么  -也没什么
- Hold on. What did you do to us? - Oh, nothing much.

235
00:10:30,300 --> 00:10:32,690
不过在你们心中放了一首歌
Just put a little song in your heart.

236
00:10:32,710 --> 00:10:34,250
放了一首...
Put a little...

237
00:10:34,270 --> 00:10:35,520
你为什么带我们来这
Why did you bring us here?

238
00:10:35,540 --> 00:10:37,920
我没带你们去哪儿
I didn't bring you anywhere.

239
00:10:37,940 --> 00:10:39,690
我们在你们脑海里
We're inside your heads.

240
00:10:39,720 --> 00:10:41,450
你们创造了这个世界
You created this world.

241
00:10:41,470 --> 00:10:43,410
算我们幸运 这里也许是战争电影
And we got lucky because it could have been a war movie

242
00:10:43,430 --> 00:10:44,850
或是... 太空歌剧
or a... a space opera,

243
00:10:43,430 --> 00:10:44,850
{\an8}以太空旅行为主题的广播剧 电视剧 电影

244
00:10:44,870 --> 00:10:47,070
但还好你们都热爱歌舞片
but thanks to your love of musicals,

245
00:10:47,100 --> 00:10:50,570
你看过无数次"绿野仙踪"
with the countless times you watched, um, "Wizard of Oz"

246
00:10:50,590 --> 00:10:52,590
-和你的养父母一起...  -你怎么知道
- with your adoptive parents... - How did you know that?

247
00:10:52,620 --> 00:10:54,110
还有你 每个雨夜都和妈妈
And, you, all those rainy nights

248
00:10:54,140 --> 00:10:56,610
看弗雷德·阿斯泰尔和弗兰克·辛纳屈的电影
watching Fred Astaire and Frank Sinatra with Mom.

249
00:10:54,140 --> 00:10:56,610
{\an8}两人均为著名歌手 演员

250
00:10:56,630 --> 00:10:58,000
难怪是歌舞片
Well, where else would we be?

251
00:10:58,020 --> 00:10:59,590
好吧 好吧
All right, all right.

252
00:11:00,970 --> 00:11:03,800
一击不中
Ooh! Swing and a miss.

253
00:11:03,820 --> 00:11:05,160
我还没说
I didn't tell you.

254
00:11:05,180 --> 00:11:06,790
我本人不在这
I'm not really here.

255
00:11:06,820 --> 00:11:08,280
我还在现实世界
See, I'm out there in the real world.

256
00:11:08,310 --> 00:11:10,170
中心城现在是我的囊中之物
Central City's mine for the taking.

257
00:11:10,200 --> 00:11:12,390
-我们会阻止你  -没错
- Ah. We're gonna stop you. - Yeah!

258
00:11:12,410 --> 00:11:14,550
放马过来
You're welcome to try that.

259
00:11:14,790 --> 00:11:16,290
前提是你们能从这逃出去
If you can get out of here.

260
00:11:16,320 --> 00:11:18,230
我们要怎么逃出去
How do we get out of here?

261
00:11:18,250 --> 00:11:20,320
你们身处一部歌舞片
You're in a movie musical.

262
00:11:20,350 --> 00:11:23,110
所以只要跟着...
So all you have to do is just follow the...

263
00:11:23,130 --> 00:11:24,330
黄砖路[出自绿野仙踪]
The Yellow Brick Road?

264
00:11:24,360 --> 00:11:25,630
不... 是剧本
No, the... the script.

265
00:11:25,630 --> 00:11:26,900
-啊 对  -剧本...
- Oh, yeah. - Script...

266
00:11:26,900 --> 00:11:28,470
剧情结束后
Reach the end of the plot,

267
00:11:28,470 --> 00:11:30,540
妈咪妈咪哄 你们就能回家了
and, presto chango, you get to go home.

268
00:11:30,540 --> 00:11:33,050
不过有件事还得说一下...
One little detail, though, I should mention...

269
00:11:33,070 --> 00:11:36,040
在这里死掉 现实世界你们也活不了
if you die in here, you die out there.

270
00:11:36,080 --> 00:11:37,160
真棒
Lovely.

271
00:11:37,190 --> 00:11:39,170
我简直受够这种魔法怪胎了
I've reached my limit with magical creeps.

272
00:11:39,190 --> 00:11:40,430
现在 我希望你们准备好
In the meantime, I hope you're both ready

273
00:11:40,450 --> 00:11:42,590
放声高歌一曲了
to get the rust off those pipes of yours.

274
00:11:42,620 --> 00:11:44,050
-我们不会为你唱歌  -不会
- We're not singing for you! - No.

275
00:11:44,050 --> 00:11:46,120
永... 永远不会 我是说
Uh, any... anymore, I mean.

276
00:11:46,140 --> 00:11:48,360
来吧 说不定一首
Come on, now, maybe just one little

277
00:11:48,360 --> 00:11:50,900
-有趣的开场小曲能...  -把外套穿上
- fun opening number just to... - Leave your jacket on.

278
00:11:50,930 --> 00:11:52,500
-...让好戏上演  -外套哪去了
- ... kick things off! - Where did it go?

279
00:11:52,530 --> 00:11:54,630
♪ 多关心你的同伴 ♪
♪ Think of your fellow man ♪

280
00:11:54,650 --> 00:11:56,050
-停下  -我们不会唱的
- Stop that. - It's not happening.

281
00:11:56,080 --> 00:11:58,380
♪ 常向他施以援手 ♪
♪ Lend him a helping hand ♪

282
00:11:58,380 --> 00:12:00,050
-没用的  -我们不唱
- It's not gonna work. - We're not singing!

283
00:12:00,070 --> 00:12:04,130
♪ 献出心里的一份爱 ♪
♪ Put a little love in your heart ♪

284
00:12:06,530 --> 00:12:08,740
♪ 你瞧时候不早了 ♪
♪ You see it's getting late ♪

285
00:12:08,770 --> 00:12:10,900
♪ 没时间犹豫了 ♪
♪ Oh, please don't hesitate ♪

286
00:12:10,900 --> 00:12:13,920
♪ 献出心里的一份爱 ♪
♪ Put a little love in your heart ♪

287
00:12:14,070 --> 00:12:15,940
♪ 全世界 ♪
♪ And the world ♪

288
00:12:15,940 --> 00:12:18,350
-♪ 全世界... ♪  -♪ 会成为美好人间 ♪
- ♪ The world... ♪ - ♪ Will be a better place ♪

289
00:12:18,370 --> 00:12:20,480
-♪ 全世界 ♪  -♪ 全世界... ♪
- ♪ And the world ♪ - ♪ The world... ♪

290
00:12:20,480 --> 00:12:22,550
♪ 会变成美好人间 ♪
♪ Will be a better place ♪

291
00:12:22,550 --> 00:12:24,690
♪ 因为你 ♪
♪ For you ♪

292
00:12:24,710 --> 00:12:26,480
♪ 还有我 ♪
♪ And me ♪

293
00:12:26,480 --> 00:12:28,670
♪ 稍加等待 ♪
♪ You just wait ♪

294
00:12:28,700 --> 00:12:31,000
♪ 就能发现 ♪
♪ And see, yeah ♪

295
00:12:31,020 --> 00:12:33,300
♪ 若想让世人知道 ♪
♪ If you want the world to know ♪

296
00:12:33,320 --> 00:12:35,120
♪ 我们不让仇恨滋长 ♪
♪ We won't let hatred grow ♪

297
00:12:35,140 --> 00:12:38,140
♪ 献出心中一份爱 ♪
♪ Put a little love in your heart ♪

298
00:12:38,160 --> 00:12:40,320
♪ 全世界 ♪
♪ And the world ♪

299
00:12:40,340 --> 00:12:42,030
♪ 将变成美好人间 ♪
♪ Will be a better place ♪

300
00:12:42,050 --> 00:12:44,040
♪ 全世界 ♪
♪ And the world ♪

301
00:12:44,110 --> 00:12:46,280
♪ 将变成美好人间 ♪
♪ Will be a better place ♪

302
00:12:46,300 --> 00:12:48,240
-♪ 因为你 ♪  -♪ 因为你 ♪
- ♪ For you ♪ - ♪ For you ♪

303
00:12:48,240 --> 00:12:49,980
-♪ 还有我 ♪  -♪ 还有我 ♪
- ♪ And me ♪ - ♪ And me ♪

304
00:12:50,000 --> 00:12:54,150
♪ 稍加等待就能发现 ♪
♪ You just wait and see ♪

305
00:12:54,170 --> 00:12:56,650
♪ 你最好瞧一瞧周围 ♪
♪ You better take a good look around ♪

306
00:12:56,650 --> 00:12:58,580
♪ 若你正低着头 ♪
♪ Oh, if you're looking down ♪

307
00:12:58,580 --> 00:13:01,670
♪ 献出心里的一份爱 ♪
♪ Put a little love in your heart ♪

308
00:13:01,700 --> 00:13:03,620
♪ 全世界 ♪
♪ And the world ♪

309
00:13:03,620 --> 00:13:05,490
♪ 将变成美好人间 ♪
♪ Will be a better place ♪

310
00:13:05,490 --> 00:13:07,510
-♪ 全世界 ♪  -♪ 全世界 ♪
- ♪ All the world ♪ - ♪ All the world ♪

311
00:13:07,530 --> 00:13:09,560
♪ 将变成美好人间 ♪
♪ Will be a better place ♪

312
00:13:09,590 --> 00:13:11,550
-♪ 因为你 ♪  -♪ 因为你 ♪
- ♪ For you ♪ - ♪ For you ♪

313
00:13:11,580 --> 00:13:13,340
-♪ 还有我 ♪  -♪ 还有我 ♪
- ♪ And me ♪ - ♪ And me ♪

314
00:13:13,360 --> 00:13:17,940
♪ 稍加等待就能发现 ♪
♪ You just wait and see ♪

315
00:13:17,970 --> 00:13:20,300
♪ 献出心中一份爱 ♪
♪ Put a little love in your heart ♪

316
00:13:20,310 --> 00:13:22,000
♪ 献出一份爱 献出一份爱 ♪
♪ Put a little love, put a little love ♪

317
00:13:22,010 --> 00:13:25,870
♪ 献出心中一份爱 ♪
♪ Put a little love in your heart ♪

318
00:13:25,890 --> 00:13:28,320
♪ 献出心中一份爱 ♪
♪ Put a little love in your heart ♪

319
00:13:28,350 --> 00:13:29,710
♪ 献出一份爱 ♪
♪ Put a little love ♪

320
00:13:29,740 --> 00:13:32,640
♪ 献出心中一份爱 ♪
♪ Put a little love in your heart ♪

321
00:13:32,670 --> 00:13:33,710
♪ 一起来... ♪
♪ Come on and... ♪

322
00:13:33,730 --> 00:13:35,720
♪ 献出心中... ♪
♪ Put a little love... ♪

323
00:13:35,750 --> 00:13:41,310
♪ 一份爱... ♪
♪ In your heart... ♪

324
00:13:45,400 --> 00:13:46,670
他去哪了
Where'd he go?

325
00:13:47,200 --> 00:13:48,570
不知道
I don't know.

326
00:13:48,590 --> 00:13:51,020
走 我们去找他
Come on, let's find him.

327
00:13:55,440 --> 00:13:56,920
-他消失了  -没错
- He's gone. - Yup.

328
00:13:56,950 --> 00:13:58,750
-现在怎么办  -不知道
- So what do we do now? - I don't know.

329
00:13:58,780 --> 00:14:01,280
大概只能...
I mean, I guess we just...

330
00:14:01,310 --> 00:14:02,780
照他说的做
we do what he says, right?

331
00:14:02,800 --> 00:14:04,400
我们得弄清楚这部歌舞片的剧情
We have to figure out what the plot of the musical is,

332
00:14:04,430 --> 00:14:06,710
-跟着故事演下去  -好吧 那...
- and we follow the story. - Okay, uh, so...

333
00:14:06,740 --> 00:14:08,640
我们现在什么设定
what do we know so far?

334
00:14:08,720 --> 00:14:09,870
我们是卖唱的
We're singers.

335
00:14:09,900 --> 00:14:12,250
而且老板是黑社会
And apparently we work for a gangster.

336
00:14:12,270 --> 00:14:14,670
没错 还要我们为他单独表演
Yes, who wants us to perform for him.

337
00:14:14,690 --> 00:14:16,680
老实说 也没那么难懂
I mean, honestly, it's pretty straightforward.

338
00:14:16,710 --> 00:14:17,840
-是吗  -对啊
- Right? - Yeah.

339
00:14:17,870 --> 00:14:19,190
你们好
Hello.

340
00:14:19,220 --> 00:14:21,620
你们好 我想念刀枪不入的超能力
Hi! I miss being bulletproof.


341
00:14:21,640 --> 00:14:23,770
-跟我们走  -谁说的
- You're coming with us. - Says who?

342
00:14:26,390 --> 00:14:27,990
我说的
Says me.

343
00:14:32,710 --> 00:14:34,140
巴里 你没事吧
Barry, are you okay?

344
00:14:34,140 --> 00:14:36,060
天啊 快别喊了
Oh, please stop yelling.

345
00:14:36,080 --> 00:14:37,850
我没喊啊
I'm not yelling.

346
00:14:39,570 --> 00:14:41,540
等等 我们这是在哪儿
Wait, where are we?

347
00:14:41,750 --> 00:14:43,200
我也不知道
I don't know.

348
00:14:43,830 --> 00:14:45,590
好吧 别担心 我相信科学之星实验室的每个人
All right, well, I'm sure everybody at S.T.A.R. Labs

349
00:14:45,610 --> 00:14:47,320
都在想办法救我们出去
is working on getting us out of this.

350
00:14:47,320 --> 00:14:49,150
是啊 多亏他们带我来你的地球
Yeah, I'm glad they brought me to your Earth.

351
00:14:50,860 --> 00:14:52,930
蒙-艾尔看起来真的很在乎你
Mon-El seems like he really cares about you.

352
00:14:54,360 --> 00:14:56,290
蒙-艾尔只在乎他自己
Mon-El only cares about himself.

353
00:14:56,320 --> 00:14:58,540
我们认识9个月他都没告诉我
He lied to me about who he really is

354
00:14:58,560 --> 00:15:00,130
他的真实身份
for nine months.

355
00:15:00,150 --> 00:15:01,680
我没办法原谅他
I can't shake it.

356
00:15:02,380 --> 00:15:04,100
我以为我们会是那种特别的关系
I thought it was gonna be something special

357
00:15:04,100 --> 00:15:05,840
像你和爱瑞斯一样
like what you have with Iris.

358
00:15:05,840 --> 00:15:07,400
我们...
That is...

359
00:15:07,410 --> 00:15:08,840
分手了
off track.

360
00:15:08,840 --> 00:15:10,140
抱歉
I'm sorry.

361
00:15:10,140 --> 00:15:11,680
我向她求婚了
I asked her to marry me.

362
00:15:11,700 --> 00:15:14,610
真的吗 太好了
You did? That's great.

363
00:15:14,640 --> 00:15:15,940
她肯定同意了吧
Did she not say yes?

364
00:15:15,960 --> 00:15:18,700
是啊 她是同意了 不过我向她求婚的理由
Oh, she said yes, but I guess I did it

365
00:15:18,720 --> 00:15:20,820
不是很正当 我当然是爱她的
for the wrong reason, and, I mean, I love her,

366
00:15:20,820 --> 00:15:23,640
不过我向她求婚是为了要改变未来
but I was trying to change the future.

367
00:15:24,120 --> 00:15:27,130
后来就分开了 想专心救她
Then I pushed her away so I could focus on saving her,

368
00:15:27,160 --> 00:15:28,990
现在简直是一团乱
and it's just a mess now.

369
00:15:29,890 --> 00:15:31,900
还是跑步简单啊
Everything's so simple when I'm running.

370
00:15:31,900 --> 00:15:33,500
飞行也不难
Or flying.

371
00:15:33,500 --> 00:15:34,760
闭嘴
Shut up!

372
00:15:34,770 --> 00:15:36,200
你们俩都给我闭嘴
Both of you.

373
00:15:36,530 --> 00:15:37,770
斯坦因
Stein?

374
00:15:37,770 --> 00:15:39,940
谁... 谁是斯坦因
Who... who's Stein?

375
00:15:40,360 --> 00:15:41,740
对 你不是
Right.

376
00:15:46,840 --> 00:15:49,350
-这就是他们  -没错
- This them? - Yeah.

377
00:15:59,350 --> 00:16:00,720
你知道我是谁吗
Do you know who I am?

378
00:16:00,730 --> 00:16:02,930
反正不是乔·韦斯特
Not Joe West, I'm guessing.

379
00:16:02,930 --> 00:16:05,270
狄格西 狄格西·福斯
Digsy. Digsy Foss.

380
00:16:05,560 --> 00:16:07,230
这城是我的
I run this town.

381
00:16:07,250 --> 00:16:09,920
那你是市长咯
So you're the mayor?

382
00:16:11,130 --> 00:16:13,570
市长虽然赢了选举...
The mayor may have gotten the vote...

383
00:16:13,570 --> 00:16:15,220
不过实权在我手里
but I got the power.

384
00:16:20,200 --> 00:16:22,130
我现在遇到点麻烦...
I got a situation...

385
00:16:22,150 --> 00:16:24,240
你们两个要帮我解决好
that you two are gonna help me with.

386
00:16:24,260 --> 00:16:26,780
-为您办事 荣幸之至  -非常乐意
- We would love to help you with it. - Really love to.

387
00:16:26,800 --> 00:16:29,010
我的女儿 米莉...
My daughter, Millie...

388
00:16:29,350 --> 00:16:30,840
失踪了
she's missing.

389
00:16:32,340 --> 00:16:33,770
最后出现在
Last she was seen,

390
00:16:33,790 --> 00:16:36,570
去往砍特·莫兰夜店的路上
she was heading into Cutter Moran's place.

391
00:16:39,810 --> 00:16:41,790
你们见到她了吗
Have you seen her in there?

392
00:16:44,570 --> 00:16:46,770
-米莉 你是说她叫米莉吗  -是啊 怎么了
- Millie, did you say? - Yeah. Why?

393
00:16:47,840 --> 00:16:48,990
我从没见过她 我没见过她
We haven't seen her. I haven't seen her.

394
00:16:49,020 --> 00:16:50,210
-我没见过她  -是啊 我们...
- I haven't seen her. - Yeah, we...

395
00:16:50,230 --> 00:16:53,550
她是我这一生...
She's the only thing that is good and decent...

396
00:16:53,580 --> 00:16:54,840
唯一的美好
about my life.

397
00:16:54,870 --> 00:16:56,230
如果她有什么三长两短
If anything happened to her,

398
00:16:56,260 --> 00:16:59,280
我就让整个城给她陪葬
this town will run red with blood.

399
00:16:59,280 --> 00:17:00,720
用你俩祭旗
Starting with yours.

400
00:17:00,720 --> 00:17:02,360
我们可不想送死 是吧
We wouldn't want that, now, right?

401
00:17:02,380 --> 00:17:03,920
那我们该如何帮你
So, um, how can we help you?

402
00:17:03,920 --> 00:17:05,260
你俩是砍特的歌手吧
You two sing for Cutter.

403
00:17:05,260 --> 00:17:07,610
-我们是  -是的 我们是
- We sure do. - Yes, we do.

404
00:17:07,630 --> 00:17:10,000
你们到处走走 看能不能找到她
You could poke around and see if you can find her.

405
00:17:11,080 --> 00:17:13,660
你们会帮我吧
So are you gonna do this for me?

406
00:17:15,650 --> 00:17:16,970
怎么办啊
What do we do?

407
00:17:16,970 --> 00:17:18,540
跟着剧本走
Follow the script.

408
00:17:20,370 --> 00:17:22,920
-我们会找到她的 先生  -没错
- We're gonna find her... sir. - Mm-hmm.

409
00:17:24,010 --> 00:17:25,920
很好
Good.

410
00:17:30,480 --> 00:17:31,880
好了
Okay.

411
00:17:31,880 --> 00:17:33,680
就是这儿
This is the place.

412
00:17:33,690 --> 00:17:35,770
4B房间
Apartment 4B.

413
00:17:35,790 --> 00:17:37,830
爱瑞斯就在这儿吗
This is where we can find Iris?

414
00:17:37,850 --> 00:17:39,180
-米莉  -对 米莉
- Millie. - Millie, right.

415
00:17:39,210 --> 00:17:40,890
没错 她就在里面
Yeah, she's in there, all right.

416
00:17:40,920 --> 00:17:42,420
你们两个听着
Now, you two listen to me.

417
00:17:42,420 --> 00:17:44,680
别告诉任何人是我带你们来的
Don't you go telling anyone I showed you this.

418
00:17:44,690 --> 00:17:45,940
当然了 我们保证
Oh, yeah, we promise.

419
00:17:45,960 --> 00:17:47,020
聪明人不用多说
Word to the wise.

420
00:17:47,040 --> 00:17:49,040
你们要还想趟这浑水的话...
You go digging around in this dirt...

421
00:17:49,390 --> 00:17:51,250
可别被门内的场景吓着
you might not like what you find.

422
00:17:52,240 --> 00:17:53,690
好的
Okay.

423
00:17:55,180 --> 00:17:57,060
好了 记住 她或许看起来很像爱瑞斯
Okay, so remember, she might look like Iris,

424
00:17:57,090 --> 00:17:58,690
但她不是
but she is not Iris.

425
00:17:58,710 --> 00:18:00,410
我知道 这一定会很奇怪
I know. This is gonna be weird.

426
00:18:00,440 --> 00:18:01,550
可不是嘛
Yeah, tell me about it.

427
00:18:01,580 --> 00:18:04,280
算我走运 没碰上长得像蒙-艾尔的人
I'm glad we haven't seen someone that looks like Mon-El.

428
00:18:04,310 --> 00:18:07,120
不然我可能真要揍他一拳玩玩儿
I'd probably just punch him in the face for the fun of it.

429
00:18:08,190 --> 00:18:09,700
哦 天啊
Oh, my God!

430
00:18:10,090 --> 00:18:11,420
是她
That's her.

431
00:18:11,450 --> 00:18:12,650
她好像有麻烦了
Sounds like she's in trouble.

432
00:18:12,670 --> 00:18:13,960
好了 往后点 我要破门而入了
Here, stand back, I'm gonna kick the door in.

433
00:18:13,990 --> 00:18:15,620
你往后点 我来踹门
You stand back, I'll kick the door in.

434
00:18:15,640 --> 00:18:16,680
我没有性别歧视你
Well, I didn't mean, like, a gender thing.

435
00:18:16,700 --> 00:18:18,090
-我只想踹门而已  -巴里
- I just wanted to kick it in... - Barry!

436
00:18:18,110 --> 00:18:19,390
好吧 一起 总行了吧
All right, together. All right?

437
00:18:19,410 --> 00:18:21,080
-一 二  -三
- One, two... - Three!

438
00:18:24,330 --> 00:18:26,700
这是什么鬼
What the hell is going on?

439
00:18:31,360 --> 00:18:33,430
好吧 被你们抓到了
All right, you caught us.

440
00:18:33,460 --> 00:18:34,920
我们谈恋爱了
We're in love.

441
00:18:35,440 --> 00:18:37,290
太恶心了
Ugh, gross.

442
00:18:43,500 --> 00:18:44,930
伙计们 我们有麻烦了
Guys, we have a problem.

443
00:18:44,940 --> 00:18:46,470
好吧 是个新麻烦
Well, another problem.

444
00:18:46,500 --> 00:18:47,940
巴里细胞中的神速力
The Speed Force levels in Barry's cells

445
00:18:47,970 --> 00:18:49,330
严重减少
have been severely depleted,

446
00:18:49,360 --> 00:18:51,720
卡拉身体里的太阳辐射也是
as has the amount of solar radiation in Kara's body.

447
00:18:51,740 --> 00:18:53,360
这是什么意思
What exactly does that mean?

448
00:18:53,380 --> 00:18:55,120
他们的能力在消失
They're being drained.

449
00:18:55,150 --> 00:18:56,800
把他们迷晕的人...
The guy who did this to them...

450
00:18:56,830 --> 00:18:59,000
他是在偷取他们的能力
I think he's stealing their powers.

451
00:19:12,350 --> 00:19:13,850
能力启动
Power up.

452
00:19:25,650 --> 00:19:26,780
我们得把他抓住
We gotta bring him in.

453
00:19:26,800 --> 00:19:28,640
不用 我自己去就行 
No, not we... me.

454
00:19:28,660 --> 00:19:30,460
是我害的巴里被迷晕的
I'm the reason Barry got whammied.

455
00:19:30,460 --> 00:19:32,110
不管输赢 我们都要同心协力 
We win and we lose as a team.

456
00:19:32,130 --> 00:19:33,370
我跟你一起去 
I'm coming with you.

457
00:19:33,390 --> 00:19:34,990
我也去
I'm coming too.

458
00:19:35,370 --> 00:19:36,610
听我说 约翰
Look, J'onn, uh,

459
00:19:36,630 --> 00:19:39,500
虽然我敬你是个特工
I respect this whole special agent situation you got going on,

460
00:19:39,530 --> 00:19:42,090
但眼下这个局面需要
but this problem right here needs someone with...

461
00:19:45,130 --> 00:19:47,930
绿皮肤穿超酷斗篷的人
green skin and sick-ass cape.

462
00:19:47,950 --> 00:19:50,280
叫我火星猎人 
Call me the Martian Manhunter.

463
00:19:50,280 --> 00:19:52,020
发现了吧 约翰其实是
I think you'll find that J'onn's a lot more than...

464
00:19:52,020 --> 00:19:53,590
帅外惠中
just a pretty face.

465
00:19:54,420 --> 00:19:56,050
伙计们 
Guys!

466
00:19:56,060 --> 00:19:57,430
你好啊 
Hello.

467
00:19:57,450 --> 00:20:00,660
巴里和卡拉的生命体征波动很大 
Also, Barry and Kara's vitals are all over the place.

468
00:20:00,690 --> 00:20:02,190
我们走 
Let's go.

469
00:20:08,510 --> 00:20:09,800
行动吧 
All right.

470
00:20:09,820 --> 00:20:11,320
朋友们 你们好 
Hello, friends!

471
00:20:11,680 --> 00:20:12,840
闪电小子
Kid Flash.

472
00:20:12,860 --> 00:20:14,600
真高兴看到你来凑热闹
Oh, I'm so glad you could join the party.

473
00:20:14,620 --> 00:20:17,500
我可是你的大粉丝 不过说实话
I'm such a huge fan of your work, but I have to say,

474
00:20:17,540 --> 00:20:20,010
你最近的表现都不在状态
recently, your work's been a bit off.

475
00:20:20,040 --> 00:20:21,180
你知道我在说什么吧 
You know what I'm talking about?

476
00:20:21,210 --> 00:20:24,130
我猜神速力里发生的故事
I think maybe it's just that you're a little scared...

477
00:20:24,150 --> 00:20:25,970
把你震住了
from what happened in the Speed Force.

478
00:20:26,000 --> 00:20:27,490
对吧 
Is that it?

479
00:20:27,490 --> 00:20:28,910
不对 
No,

480
00:20:29,120 --> 00:20:31,580
我现在已经无所畏惧了 
and I'm not afraid of anything.

481
00:20:31,940 --> 00:20:33,470
拭目以待吧 
Prove it.

482
00:20:47,010 --> 00:20:49,740
西斯科 他们朝着第四大道和白杨路方向去了 
Uh, Cisco, they're headed towards 4th and Aspen.

483
00:20:49,740 --> 00:20:50,940
收到
Got it.

484
00:20:50,960 --> 00:20:52,200
这边走
This way.

485
00:21:05,920 --> 00:21:07,260
接下来 约翰 
All right, J'onn,

486
00:21:07,260 --> 00:21:09,130
要不要来个强强联手啊 
how do you feel about a little one-two combo?

487
00:21:09,130 --> 00:21:10,760
我这就打开一个缺口 你做好准备
I'm gonna open a breach, you be ready to hit something

488
00:21:10,760 --> 00:21:12,200
对准另一头全力出击
really hard on the B-side.

489
00:21:12,200 --> 00:21:13,770
往死里打 我擅长 
Hitting hard, I can do.

490
00:21:13,770 --> 00:21:16,310
沃利 准备好在地面发起攻击 
Wally, get ready to do the same thing on the ground level.

491
00:21:16,330 --> 00:21:17,850
收到 
Copy.

492
00:21:20,460 --> 00:21:21,660
动手 
Now!

493
00:21:46,150 --> 00:21:47,650
做个好梦 
Nighty-night.

494
00:21:49,100 --> 00:21:50,500
你是们谁啊 
Hey, who are you?

495
00:21:50,500 --> 00:21:52,240
快说你们叫什么 
Your names, now.

496
00:21:52,280 --> 00:21:53,710
我叫卡拉 他是巴里 
I'm Kara. This is Barry.

497
00:21:53,740 --> 00:21:56,700
我们都在你父亲的夜总会唱歌
We're singers at your dad's nightclub.

498
00:21:56,720 --> 00:22:00,440
是的 米莉 你父亲还以为你被绑架了 
Yeah, Millie, your dad thinks you've been kidnapped.

499
00:22:00,470 --> 00:22:02,390
好吧 很明显他弄错了 
Well, clearly he's mistaken.

500
00:22:02,420 --> 00:22:04,090
他特别想让你回家 
He really wants you to come home.

501
00:22:04,110 --> 00:22:06,350
-听着 我才不会回去呢  -嗯哼 
- Listen, I am never going back there. - Mm-mm.

502
00:22:06,370 --> 00:22:09,620
为什么不 没有地方比家更好 
Why not? There's no place like home.

503
00:22:12,760 --> 00:22:14,730
汤米·莫兰在哪里 
Tommy Moran...

504
00:22:14,830 --> 00:22:16,420
哪里就是家 
is my home.

505
00:22:16,710 --> 00:22:19,230
再说了 要是老头子们撞破我们的恋情 
And besides, if our geezers ever caught wind of this,

506
00:22:19,230 --> 00:22:20,570
肯定又是一场恶战
they'd go to war.

507
00:22:20,600 --> 00:22:22,900
不只是我们的恋情要走向终结 
It'd be the end of more than just us, huh?

508
00:22:22,900 --> 00:22:24,670
对 汤米说得没错 
Yeah, Tommy's right.

509
00:22:24,670 --> 00:22:26,560
我们的父亲是死对头
Our fathers hate each other.

510
00:22:26,710 --> 00:22:28,770
我们这是禁忌之恋
Our love is forbidden.

511
00:22:29,010 --> 00:22:31,010
这就是"西区故事"[禁忌恋电影]的情节 
This is just like "West Side Story."

512
00:22:31,010 --> 00:22:32,570
我觉得更像"异想天开"[音乐剧] 不过...
I was thinking more "Fantasticks," but...

513
00:22:32,590 --> 00:22:34,620
听好了 重点就是
Look, the point is...

514
00:22:34,950 --> 00:22:37,180
我们绝不会走漏风声 
we ain't telling nobody nothing.

515
00:22:37,210 --> 00:22:39,480
你们也要守口如瓶 懂了吗
And neither are you, capisce?

516
00:22:39,490 --> 00:22:40,980
懂了 
"Capisce."

517
00:22:41,000 --> 00:22:43,370
能让我们单独聊聊吗 
Can you give us a second?

518
00:22:44,460 --> 00:22:45,480
可以
Sure.

519
00:22:45,500 --> 00:22:48,460
他说我们要按着剧本演 
Okay, look, he says we need to follow the script.

520
00:22:48,490 --> 00:22:49,710
对吧 我们在歌舞剧里 
Right? We're in a musical.

521
00:22:49,710 --> 00:22:51,100
我想着若是能说服他们 
So I think if we convince them

522
00:22:51,130 --> 00:22:52,490
向各自的父亲坦白恋情 
to tell their fathers that they're in love,

523
00:22:52,520 --> 00:22:53,700
也许我们就能从这里逃出去了 
maybe that'll get us out of here.

524
00:22:53,700 --> 00:22:56,370
回去继续做...
And back home to being...

525
00:22:56,370 --> 00:22:58,340
单身狗 真好...
single, yay...

526
00:22:58,360 --> 00:22:59,740
至少我们俩能一起单 
At least we'll be single together.

527
00:22:59,750 --> 00:23:01,750
这么说真的能安慰人吗 
Has saying that ever made anyone feel better?

528
00:23:01,770 --> 00:23:03,210
不好说 
Debatable.

529
00:23:03,390 --> 00:23:05,200
好了 听着...
Okay, so look...

530
00:23:05,230 --> 00:23:06,750
你们的父亲都不是完美无缺 对吧
your fathers aren't perfect, right?

531
00:23:06,780 --> 00:23:08,780
爱情也不是完美无缺 
Love isn't perfect.

532
00:23:08,780 --> 00:23:12,080
不是 但是不能因为爱上一个人 
No, but you can't let your love for somebody

533
00:23:12,090 --> 00:23:14,890
就为尚未发生之事而担惊受怕
cause you to be afraid of what might happen.

534
00:23:14,920 --> 00:23:16,900
不论如何 好坏都要一起承受
You gotta take the good with the bad, no matter what.

535
00:23:16,920 --> 00:23:19,230
-说的对  -这就意味着...
- Right. - And that includes...

536
00:23:19,260 --> 00:23:22,050
要向你们的父亲坦白彼此之间的爱意 
telling your fathers how you two feel about each other.

537
00:23:25,970 --> 00:23:27,390
好了 你说的有道理 
All right, you make a convincing argument.

538
00:23:27,420 --> 00:23:28,430
-确实  -我们会去说 
- You do. - We'll do it.

539
00:23:28,450 --> 00:23:29,590
我们会坦白恋情 不是吗 
We'll tell them about us, right?

540
00:23:29,610 --> 00:23:30,750
好啊 我们现在就去 
Well, we should go now.

541
00:23:30,780 --> 00:23:32,380
-哇 多谢啦 小子  -好吧 
- Gee, thanks, kid. - Okay.

542
00:23:33,050 --> 00:23:34,600
-为了你  -谢谢你 
- For you. - Thank you.

543
00:23:36,760 --> 00:23:38,710
好吧...
Okay, uh...

544
00:23:38,740 --> 00:23:41,340
歌舞剧里说服人真是...
convincing people in musicals is...

545
00:23:41,410 --> 00:23:43,120
-... 太太太容易了  -是啊 
- ... really easy. - Yeah.

546
00:23:43,180 --> 00:23:46,080
希望从这里出去也这么容易
Let's hope getting out of one is just as easy.

547
00:23:48,700 --> 00:23:49,790
看吧 
Digsy!

548
00:23:49,820 --> 00:23:51,330
她回来了 
She's back!

549
00:23:54,730 --> 00:23:56,290
谢天谢地你没事 
Thank God you're safe.

550
00:23:56,320 --> 00:23:58,910
我当然没事啦 
Oh, of course I'm safe.

551
00:23:59,570 --> 00:24:02,840
巴里和卡拉告诉我 你派他们去找我 
Barry and Kara told me that you sent them to find me.

552
00:24:02,860 --> 00:24:04,270
我们都很担心你 
We were concerned.

553
00:24:04,300 --> 00:24:07,550
老爸们 有什么好担心的啊 
Dads, there's no reason to be concerned.

554
00:24:07,580 --> 00:24:09,040
"老爸们"
"Dads"?

555
00:24:09,400 --> 00:24:11,170
你有意见啊 
You got a problem with that?

556
00:24:11,190 --> 00:24:12,450
没 
No.

557
00:24:12,840 --> 00:24:15,850
我热爱歌舞剧 
I love musicals, so...

558
00:24:15,870 --> 00:24:17,350
好吧 
Okay...

559
00:24:17,850 --> 00:24:22,290
听我说 老爸们 有件事 
Look, Dads, there's something that...

560
00:24:22,310 --> 00:24:24,600
我得告诉你们 
I need to tell you.

561
00:24:26,730 --> 00:24:28,190
我谈恋爱啦 
I'm in love!

562
00:24:32,700 --> 00:24:36,130
那个幸运的小子是谁啊 
Who is the, uh... the lucky boy?

563
00:24:42,060 --> 00:24:43,540
汤米·莫兰
Tommy Moran.

564
00:24:43,570 --> 00:24:46,220
你... 你是指砍特·莫兰的小子？
You... you mean Cutter Moran's kid?

565
00:24:46,250 --> 00:24:47,930
老爸 听着 我们非常相爱
Dad, look, we're in love.

566
00:24:47,950 --> 00:24:49,980
-真是见鬼  -他就是个小流氓
- The hell you are. - He's a hooligan!

567
00:24:50,010 --> 00:24:51,640
他父亲是个流氓
His father's a hooligan.

568
00:24:51,670 --> 00:24:52,930
他母亲是个... 
His mother is...

569
00:24:52,960 --> 00:24:54,730
不要在女儿面前说
Not in front of the girl.

570
00:24:54,750 --> 00:24:56,450
我不准你和他在一起
And you're not loving that boy.

571
00:24:57,990 --> 00:24:59,760
你疯了吗
Have you lost your mind?

572
00:24:59,760 --> 00:25:02,290
她是敌人的女儿
She is the daughter of my enemy.

573
00:25:02,300 --> 00:25:05,150
狄格西·福斯就是个肮脏下流的无赖
Digsy Foss is a dirty, rotten scoundrel,

574
00:25:05,180 --> 00:25:06,760
他女儿也不会是什么好东西...
and the apple doesn't fall far from the tree...

575
00:25:06,770 --> 00:25:08,230
老爸 听我解释
Dad, if you just let me explain.

576
00:25:08,230 --> 00:25:10,210
没什么好解释的 汤米
There's nothing to explain, Tommy.

577
00:25:11,600 --> 00:25:14,200
我知道你一直有什么瞒着我
I knew you were keeping something from me.

578
00:25:15,040 --> 00:25:18,050
没想到竟是这个
I never imagined it was something like this!

579
00:25:18,080 --> 00:25:20,690
她不再是你们的小公主了
She isn't your little girl anymore.

580
00:25:21,300 --> 00:25:22,970
她长大了
Well, she isn't.

581
00:25:23,000 --> 00:25:25,530
她是个非常勇敢 强大的女人
She's an incredibly brave, strong woman.

582
00:25:25,560 --> 00:25:27,350
只要你们认真看就能看到
One look, and you can see that.

583
00:25:27,350 --> 00:25:29,580
她希望能和他在一起
And she wants to be with him.

584
00:25:29,770 --> 00:25:31,680
不论告诉你们需要多大的勇气
No matter how scared she was to tell you,

585
00:25:31,710 --> 00:25:34,380
不论和他在一起会有多么危险
no matter how dangerous it is to be with him,

586
00:25:34,570 --> 00:25:36,990
最重要的是 他们与彼此在一起
all that matters is, they're together.

587
00:25:37,540 --> 00:25:39,460
当你遇到这样的爱情
And when you find a love like that, well...

588
00:25:39,470 --> 00:25:40,910
一定要紧紧握住它
you gotta hold on to it.

589
00:25:40,930 --> 00:25:43,200
无论谁阻止你
No matter who's trying to stop you.

590
00:25:44,470 --> 00:25:46,450
我对这点深信不疑
That's clear to me now.

591
00:25:46,670 --> 00:25:49,270
我觉得你对你儿子有些太过严厉了
I think you're being a little tough on your son.

592
00:25:49,280 --> 00:25:50,430
什么
Excuse me?

593
00:25:50,460 --> 00:25:52,750
他为什么不马上告诉你 显而易见嘛
Well, it's obvious why he didn't tell you right away.

594
00:25:52,780 --> 00:25:55,210
看看你现在的反应
I mean, look at the way you're reacting.

595
00:25:55,350 --> 00:25:59,350
也许你只要静下心来... 听听他解释
Maybe if you just listen and... and hear his reasons

596
00:25:59,350 --> 00:26:02,690
试着设身处地为他考虑...
and try to see things from his point of view...

597
00:26:03,680 --> 00:26:06,090
也许... 也许你就能理解为什么
maybe... maybe you'd understand why

598
00:26:06,090 --> 00:26:08,260
他从前会...
he didn't tell you...

599
00:26:08,260 --> 00:26:09,700
瞒着你
before now.

600
00:26:12,120 --> 00:26:14,220
宝贝女儿 这一切...
Baby doll, it's just...

601
00:26:14,440 --> 00:26:16,740
你永远无法理解为人父亲的焦虑
you'll never understand what it means to be a father.

602
00:26:16,760 --> 00:26:19,430
米莉 亲爱的 我们会一直照顾着你
Millie, my darling, we've always taken care of you.

603
00:26:19,430 --> 00:26:21,910
我们只希望你幸福
We just want you to be happy.

604
00:26:27,570 --> 00:26:30,210
♪ 沃尔福特 我可以祝福你 ♪ 
♪ Velvet, I can wish you ♪

605
00:26:30,240 --> 00:26:33,920
♪ 大衣的衣领 ♪ 
♪ For the collar of your coat ♪

606
00:26:34,190 --> 00:26:36,120
♪ 和美丽的笑容 ♪ 
♪ And fortune smiling... ♪

607
00:26:36,140 --> 00:26:39,980
♪ 都与你随行 ♪ 
♪ All along your way ♪

608
00:26:40,410 --> 00:26:43,670
♪ 除此之外 ♪ 
♪ But more I cannot wish you ♪

609
00:26:43,700 --> 00:26:47,730
♪ 我希望你能找到真爱 ♪ 
♪ Than to wish you find your love ♪

610
00:26:47,730 --> 00:26:50,730
♪ 属于你的真爱 ♪ 
♪ Your own true love ♪

611
00:26:50,760 --> 00:26:54,150
♪ 今时今日 ♪ 
♪ This day ♪

612
00:26:54,890 --> 00:26:57,800
♪ 曼森斯 我希望你 ♪  
♪ Mansions, I can wish you ♪

613
00:26:57,820 --> 00:27:01,460
♪ 七个红衣男仆 ♪ 
♪ Seven footmen, all in red ♪

614
00:27:01,600 --> 00:27:07,010
♪ 来回传着银盘子 ♪ 
♪ And calling cards upon a silver tray ♪

615
00:27:08,520 --> 00:27:11,520
♪ 除此之外 ♪ 
♪ But more I cannot wish you ♪

616
00:27:11,550 --> 00:27:15,020
♪ 我希望你能找到真爱 ♪ 
♪ Than to wish you find your love ♪

617
00:27:15,130 --> 00:27:18,260
♪ 属于你的真爱 ♪ 
♪ Your own true love ♪

618
00:27:18,290 --> 00:27:21,050
♪ 今时今日 ♪ 
♪ This day ♪

619
00:27:22,140 --> 00:27:25,400
♪ 站在那 ♪ 
♪ Standing there ♪

620
00:27:25,410 --> 00:27:28,560
♪ 凝视着你 ♪ 
♪ Gazing at you ♪

621
00:27:28,590 --> 00:27:32,040
♪ 羊羔般的眼睛 ♪ 
♪ With the sheep's eye ♪

622
00:27:32,040 --> 00:27:36,880
♪ 甘草般的牙齿 ♪ 
♪ And a licorice tooth ♪

623
00:27:37,520 --> 00:27:40,300
♪ 音乐啊我希望你 ♪ 
♪ Music I can wish you ♪

624
00:27:40,550 --> 00:27:43,750
♪ 在年轻时与快乐相伴 ♪ 
♪ Merry music while you're young ♪

625
00:27:43,760 --> 00:27:46,760
♪ 年老时 ♪ 
♪ And wisdom when your hair ♪

626
00:27:46,760 --> 00:27:50,460
♪ 与智慧为伍 ♪ 
♪ Has turned to gray ♪

627
00:27:51,400 --> 00:27:54,140
♪ 除此之外我希望 ♪ 
♪ But more I cannot wish you ♪

628
00:27:54,170 --> 00:27:57,480
♪ 你能找到真爱 ♪ 
♪ Than to wish you find your love ♪

629
00:27:57,500 --> 00:28:00,750
♪ 属于你的真爱 ♪ 
♪ Your own true love ♪

630
00:28:00,780 --> 00:28:03,370
♪ 今时今日 ♪ 
♪ This day ♪

631
00:28:04,710 --> 00:28:08,010
♪ 羊羔般的眼睛 ♪ 
♪ With a sheep's eye ♪

632
00:28:08,010 --> 00:28:10,840
♪ 甘草般的牙齿 ♪ 
♪ And a licorice tooth ♪

633
00:28:10,870 --> 00:28:13,430
♪ 还有宽厚的臂膀 ♪ 
♪ And the strong arms ♪

634
00:28:13,450 --> 00:28:16,250
♪ 带你远行 ♪ 
♪ To carry you away ♪

635
00:28:16,260 --> 00:28:17,860
♪ 远行 ♪ 
♪ Away ♪

636
00:28:17,860 --> 00:28:20,460
♪ 还有宽厚的臂膀 ♪ 
♪ And the strong arms ♪

637
00:28:20,460 --> 00:28:24,220
♪ 带你... ♪ 
♪ To carry you... ♪

638
00:28:24,440 --> 00:28:29,830
♪ 远行 ♪ 
♪ Away ♪

639
00:28:35,380 --> 00:28:37,010
谢谢你和我们说实话 宝贝
Thanks for telling us the truth, baby.

640
00:28:37,040 --> 00:28:39,280
我好爱好爱你们
I love you both so much.

641
00:28:39,300 --> 00:28:41,170
我们也爱你
We love you.

642
00:28:48,190 --> 00:28:49,740
谢了
Thanks.

643
00:28:50,360 --> 00:28:52,120
好了...
Okay...

644
00:28:54,770 --> 00:28:56,690
你想干嘛
So what do you want to do?

645
00:28:58,410 --> 00:29:00,480
叫上兄弟们
Gather up the boys.

646
00:29:01,070 --> 00:29:03,630
-要开战了  -我就知道
- We're going to war. - I had a feeling.

647
00:29:03,810 --> 00:29:06,130
我很赞赏你的诚恳 儿子
I appreciate your honesty, son.

648
00:29:06,310 --> 00:29:08,380
-谢谢 老爸  -过来
- Thanks, Dad. - Come here.

649
00:29:16,970 --> 00:29:18,400
召集人手
Get the boys.

650
00:29:18,430 --> 00:29:19,850
准备开战
We are going to war.

651
00:29:29,370 --> 00:29:30,960
果然是我最希望
if it isn't the two people

652
00:29:30,990 --> 00:29:33,770
见到的两个人
I was hoping would visit me the most.

653
00:29:33,770 --> 00:29:36,040
马上叫醒他们
Fix them. Now.

654
00:29:36,040 --> 00:29:38,240
抱歉 我做不到
I'm sorry. I can't.

655
00:29:38,260 --> 00:29:39,810
如果你还希望在有生之年从这牢房里出去
If you ever want to get out of that cell,

656
00:29:39,840 --> 00:29:41,600
那就赶紧叫醒他们
that's exactly what you're gonna do.

657
00:29:44,250 --> 00:29:46,270
你没听懂
You don't get it.

658
00:29:46,450 --> 00:29:48,020
你没明白 大个子
You don't understand, big guy.

659
00:29:48,020 --> 00:29:49,260
这是没法改变的
That's just not how it works.

660
00:29:49,260 --> 00:29:51,460
我也无能为力
My powers don't work that way.

661
00:29:51,460 --> 00:29:52,870
什么意思 是你让他们变成这样的
What do you mean? You're the one who did this to them.

662
00:29:52,890 --> 00:29:54,430
没错 但是...
Yes, but...

663
00:29:54,450 --> 00:29:55,840
他们的命运
they are the only ones that are in control

664
00:29:55,860 --> 00:29:57,560
现在由他们自己掌控
of what happens to them now,

665
00:29:57,570 --> 00:29:59,690
就像你们两一样
as are the two of you.

666
00:30:01,060 --> 00:30:02,980
我们 什么意思
Us? What does that mean?

667
00:30:03,000 --> 00:30:04,580
你有...
How much...

668
00:30:04,610 --> 00:30:06,940
多爱他 爱瑞斯
do you love him, Iris?

669
00:30:07,110 --> 00:30:11,080
还有你 蒙·艾尔 你爱她吗
And you, Mon-El, how much do you love her?

670
00:30:11,530 --> 00:30:12,920
所以问题就是
So the question is:

671
00:30:12,950 --> 00:30:16,250
你们的爱能否强大到救出他们
is that strong enough to save them?

672
00:30:17,480 --> 00:30:20,030
你们想让卡拉和巴里从那个世界回来
You want Kara and Barry back from the world they're in,

673
00:30:20,060 --> 00:30:21,960
就凭自己的力量去救他们
you can go get them yourselves.

674
00:30:21,980 --> 00:30:24,080
你们有那份力量
You have that power.

675
00:30:24,110 --> 00:30:25,610
怎么做
How?

676
00:30:25,940 --> 00:30:29,240
恕难相告 抱歉 你们得自己琢磨出来
Ah, I can't tell you. Sorry, you gotta figure it out yourself.

677
00:30:29,260 --> 00:30:30,860
现在 如果你们不介意的话 我要在这个
Now, if you don't mind, I'm gonna just chill

678
00:30:30,880 --> 00:30:33,640
金碧辉煌的小牢房里休息了
in this wonderfully decorated little cell of yours.

679
00:30:33,670 --> 00:30:35,100
再见了 朋友们
Bye, guys!

680
00:30:35,120 --> 00:30:37,220
祝你们好运 爱会告诉你们方法的
Good luck. Love will find a way.

681
00:30:37,280 --> 00:30:40,080
你们可以做到的 爱的力量是无穷的
You can do it. Power of love and all that.

682
00:30:43,010 --> 00:30:44,680
我们现在该做什么 我们让...
What do we do now? We got...

683
00:30:44,700 --> 00:30:46,880
米莉和汤米...
we got Millie and Tommy

684
00:30:46,910 --> 00:30:48,360
告诉了他们的父亲他们在一起了
to tell their fathers that they're in love.

685
00:30:48,390 --> 00:30:50,820
虽然我知道是在歌舞剧里
Which, I know we're in a musical and everything,

686
00:30:50,820 --> 00:30:53,300
但看见蒙·艾尔和别人在一起...
but seeing Mon-El in love with someone else was...

687
00:30:53,320 --> 00:30:55,650
看着很不爽 我懂
It was hard to watch. I know.

688
00:30:55,660 --> 00:30:57,620
不管了 我们现在...
Anyway, I mean, what are we...

689
00:30:57,650 --> 00:30:59,790
怎么办 你觉得这所谓的...
supposed to do? What do you think this...

690
00:30:59,790 --> 00:31:01,990
音乐大师到底要我们干嘛
Music Meister needs us to do now?

692
00:31:03,430 --> 00:31:04,830
终于找到你们了
Ah, there you are!

693
00:31:04,830 --> 00:31:06,000
准备好了吗
You two ready?

694
00:31:06,000 --> 00:31:07,630
准备啥来着...
Ready for...

695
00:31:08,050 --> 00:31:10,220
排练啊 笨蛋
For rehearsal, you dolt.

696
00:31:10,240 --> 00:31:13,170
莫兰先生说你有很多原创歌曲
Mr. Moran told me that you got more songs in your repertoire.

697
00:31:13,170 --> 00:31:15,040
我们要演完音乐剧
We have to finish the musical.

698
00:31:15,040 --> 00:31:16,810
-是啊  -那你...
- Yeah. - Uh, do you...

699
00:31:16,810 --> 00:31:18,980
你有原创曲子吗
do you happen to know anything original?

700
00:31:19,000 --> 00:31:20,840
不骗你们
As a matter of fact,

701
00:31:20,870 --> 00:31:23,350
我整天都在创作
I've been working on something all day..

703
00:31:24,680 --> 00:31:27,990
-音乐剧里真轻松  -可不是
- Things really are easier in musicals. - Yeah.

704
00:31:31,610 --> 00:31:32,910
开始
All right.

705
00:31:33,720 --> 00:31:36,010
♪ 此时此刻 ♪
♪ At times like these ♪

706
00:31:36,030 --> 00:31:38,580
♪ 生活受挫 ♪
♪ When life is getting me down ♪

707
00:31:38,600 --> 00:31:42,860
♪ 世界看似要分崩 ♪
♪ And the world seems like it's gonna end-ship ♪

708
00:31:42,880 --> 00:31:45,190
♪ 至少我还有支撑 ♪
♪ There's at least one power ♪

709
00:31:45,210 --> 00:31:47,750
♪ 你我共所享 ♪
♪ That we both still have ♪

710
00:31:47,770 --> 00:31:50,340
♪ 那正是... ♪
♪ And that's the power of... ♪

711
00:31:50,360 --> 00:31:52,240
♪ 友谊的力量 ♪
♪ Friendship? ♪

712
00:31:52,400 --> 00:31:53,920
跟我想一块儿了
Yeah, that's exactly what I was gonna say.

713
00:31:53,950 --> 00:31:55,530
这节奏挺简单
Yeah, it's an easy rhyme.

714
00:31:55,880 --> 00:31:58,030
♪ 我是你的超级朋友 ♪
♪ I'm your super friend ♪

715
00:31:59,650 --> 00:32:02,290
♪ 你的超级朋友 ♪
♪ Your super friend ♪

716
00:32:02,560 --> 00:32:05,390
♪ 你若有难时 ♪
♪ I'll be there in the nick of time ♪

717
00:32:05,390 --> 00:32:08,330
♪ 我会来相帮 ♪
♪ If you're ever in a spot ♪

718
00:32:08,630 --> 00:32:10,440
♪ 若是赶不上 ♪
♪ And if you're not there in time ♪

719
00:32:10,470 --> 00:32:12,150
♪ 亦可跑回过去 ♪
♪ You can just go back in time ♪

720
00:32:12,170 --> 00:32:14,570
♪ 再次出手相帮 ♪
♪ And give it another shot ♪

721
00:32:14,600 --> 00:32:16,460
我再也不会穿回过去了
I'm actually not supposed to do that anymore.

722
00:32:16,490 --> 00:32:17,750
好吧
Oh, okay.

723
00:32:17,780 --> 00:32:19,110
继续唱
Sing!

724
00:32:19,140 --> 00:32:22,270
♪ 我是你的超级朋友 ♪
♪ I'm your super friend ♪

725
00:32:22,740 --> 00:32:25,570
♪ 超级朋友 ♪
♪ Super friend ♪

726
00:32:25,710 --> 00:32:28,470
♪ 你若要人夸奖 ♪
♪ When you need a compliment ♪

727
00:32:28,500 --> 00:32:31,750
♪ 我会不吝赞扬 ♪
♪ I can rattle off a dozen ♪

728
00:32:32,110 --> 00:32:35,280
对了 不得不说 其实你不算很惊艳
For instance, I have to say, I'm not impressed...

729
00:32:35,540 --> 00:32:38,440
♪ 不如你那表弟名声远扬 ♪
♪ By your more famous cousin ♪

730
00:32:38,470 --> 00:32:40,460
谢了你了 从没人这么说
Thank you! No one ever says that.

731
00:32:40,490 --> 00:32:42,390
他整天绷着脸说 "我是超人"
Oh, he's all, like, "I'm Superman.

732
00:32:47,100 --> 00:32:50,540
♪ 我是你的超级朋友 ♪
♪ I'm your super friend ♪

733
00:32:51,140 --> 00:32:53,330
♪ 你的超级朋友 ♪
♪ Super friend ♪

734
00:32:53,360 --> 00:32:56,420
♪ 要说谁是好兄弟 那就非你莫属 ♪
♪ When it comes to buddies, pal, you're the best ♪

735
00:32:56,450 --> 00:32:58,480
♪ 我爱你 胜过胸口 ♪
♪ I love you more than the lightning bolt ♪

736
00:32:58,510 --> 00:33:00,390
♪ 那闪电胸章 ♪
♪ I wear on my chest ♪

737
00:33:00,410 --> 00:33:01,600
♪ 若你难过心伤... ♪
♪ If you're ever sad... ♪

738
00:33:01,620 --> 00:33:03,590
♪ 我会鲜花捧上 ♪
♪ I'll bring you flowers ♪

739
00:33:03,620 --> 00:33:07,400
♪ 女高音也该算进超能力 ♪
♪ And you can list soprano as one of your powers ♪

740
00:33:07,430 --> 00:33:10,090
- ♪ 若你一时心伤 ♪  - ♪ 在我沙发上 ♪
- ♪ If you're ever broke ♪ - ♪ I've got the cash ♪

741
00:33:10,090 --> 00:33:13,150
- ♪ 钞票正闲躺 ♪  - ♪ 恭候你挥扬 ♪
- ♪ On my couch ♪ - ♪ You're welcome to crash ♪

742
00:33:13,180 --> 00:33:15,160
♪ 若你缺人帮忙 ♪
♪ And if you ever need a hand ♪

743
00:33:15,160 --> 00:33:16,960
♪ 我会瞬间闪来 ♪
♪ I'll be there in a flash ♪

744
00:33:16,980 --> 00:33:18,490
-巴里  -挺有趣的啊
- Barry! - That was funny.

745
00:33:19,670 --> 00:33:21,130
♪ 我是你的超级...  ♪
♪ I'm your super... ♪

746
00:33:21,140 --> 00:33:22,770
♪ 有话外音嘛 ♪
♪ That has a double meaning ♪

747
00:33:22,770 --> 00:33:26,760
♪ 朋友 ♪
♪ Friend ♪

748
00:33:32,280 --> 00:33:34,100
好久不见 朋友
Hello, my friend.

749
00:33:34,620 --> 00:33:37,750
你我两家
It will be a cold day in hell

750
00:33:37,780 --> 00:33:40,780
喜结连理前 必有场血雨腥风
before our daughter marries any son of yours.

751
00:33:40,810 --> 00:33:44,360
对 血雨腥风
Like he said. A cold, cold day.

752
00:33:45,670 --> 00:33:48,000
看来咱们不谋而合
You took the words right out of my mouth.

753
00:33:52,290 --> 00:33:53,390
不是吧
Come on.

754
00:33:56,040 --> 00:33:57,200
停火
Stop!


756
00:34:07,200 --> 00:34:08,440
巴里
Barry!

757
00:34:08,880 --> 00:34:10,550
天呐
Oh, my God.!

759
00:34:17,820 --> 00:34:20,240
-怎么了  -他们不行了
- What's wrong? - I think we're losing them.

760
00:34:21,360 --> 00:34:24,150
-你有办法救他们吗  -我不知道哪里出问题
- Can you stop it? - Not if I don't know why.

761
00:34:24,180 --> 00:34:26,730
怎么办 
What are we gonna do?

762
00:34:28,680 --> 00:34:30,740
一定要赶去他们的世界
We need to go to whatever world they're in.

763
00:34:30,770 --> 00:34:32,230
这怎么去
How are we gonna do that?

764
00:34:32,250 --> 00:34:34,600
他说如果我们真心爱他们
Look, he said, if we loved them enough

765
00:34:34,620 --> 00:34:36,560
不管在哪儿 都能赶去救他们
that we could save them, wherever they are.

766
00:34:38,230 --> 00:34:39,790
西斯科 用震波送我们去
Cisco, you can vibe us there.

767
00:34:39,810 --> 00:34:41,250
怕是做不到吧
I don't think it works that way.

768
00:34:41,280 --> 00:34:42,350
你带我去过神速力
You sent me into the Speed Force.

769
00:34:42,370 --> 00:34:43,960
送巴里和沃利去过未来
You sent Barry and Wally into the future.

770
00:34:43,990 --> 00:34:46,690
-这次一样  -她说什么呢
- You can do this too. - What is she talking about?

771
00:34:47,250 --> 00:34:49,050
-震波是啥  -说来话长
- What's a vibe? - I'll explain later.

772
00:34:49,060 --> 00:34:51,830
行吧 抓着我肩膀
Come on, just... grab on to my shoulders.

773
00:34:52,410 --> 00:34:54,380
希望能成吧
Let's hope this works.

774
00:34:57,330 --> 00:34:59,330
巴里 巴里...
Barry, Barry...

775
00:35:02,740 --> 00:35:04,300
卡拉...
Kara...

776
00:35:09,510 --> 00:35:10,600
巴里
Barry!

777
00:35:10,630 --> 00:35:11,990
卡拉
Kara!

778
00:35:12,020 --> 00:35:13,660
-别死  -不要
- Oh, no. - No.

779
00:35:13,680 --> 00:35:14,800
是我啊
Hey, it's me.

780
00:35:14,820 --> 00:35:16,520
是爱瑞斯 我来了
It's Iris, I'm here. Hi.

781
00:35:18,690 --> 00:35:20,520
醒醒 我会救你出去的
Stay with me. I'm gonna get you out.

782
00:35:22,150 --> 00:35:23,770
没时间了
There's no time.

783
00:35:24,060 --> 00:35:25,490
我们得赶紧走
We have to go.

784
00:35:25,520 --> 00:35:27,020
赶紧救他们出去
We have to get them out!

785
00:35:29,250 --> 00:35:31,530
醒醒 巴里
Come on, Barry. Barry!

786
00:35:32,230 --> 00:35:33,720
不要
No!

787
00:35:34,130 --> 00:35:36,510
我瞒着你是我不好
I'm so sorry I lied to you.

788
00:35:37,280 --> 00:35:38,790
我原谅你了
I forgive you.

789
00:35:41,360 --> 00:35:42,820
我爱你
I love you.

790
00:35:42,850 --> 00:35:45,010
巴里 坚持住 你会没事的
No, Barry, Barry, you're gonna be okay.

791
00:35:46,630 --> 00:35:47,890
不
No.

792
00:35:49,560 --> 00:35:51,180
我爱你
I love you.

793
00:36:01,580 --> 00:36:03,000
爱瑞斯
Iris?

794
00:36:10,830 --> 00:36:12,530
蒙-艾尔
Mon-El?

796
00:36:16,830 --> 00:36:18,680
他们回来了
They're back!

797
00:36:25,790 --> 00:36:28,320
太好了 热烈欢迎
Bravo! Round of applause!

798
00:36:28,340 --> 00:36:30,390
忍不住鼓掌 太赞了
Standing O. That was so good!

799
00:36:30,460 --> 00:36:32,400
这剧我喜欢
I loved it. That was a hell of a show.

800
00:36:32,430 --> 00:36:33,860
你们...
And you two...

801
00:36:33,860 --> 00:36:36,400
你们的爱还真是固若金汤
I guess your love really was strong enough after all.


802
00:36:36,420 --> 00:36:37,880
简直是精彩绝伦
Beautiful.

803
00:36:37,900 --> 00:36:39,670
大兄弟 你怎么逃出来的
Man, how did you get out of the cell?

804
00:36:39,670 --> 00:36:41,670
西斯科 你真觉得那牢房
Cisco, do you really think that cell

805
00:36:41,670 --> 00:36:43,940
能困住我吗
is gonna just, like, hold me?

806
00:36:43,960 --> 00:36:45,070
所以这是... 发生了什么
No, I'm sorry... what's going on?

807
00:36:45,090 --> 00:36:46,630
为什么这么做
Why did you do this to us?

808
00:36:46,650 --> 00:36:49,620
因为我相信你们是正直的人
I did it because I believe in the good guys.

809
00:36:50,450 --> 00:36:52,110
我们初次见面就说了
I told you when we first met.

810
00:36:52,110 --> 00:36:55,420
要给你们好好上一课
It was to teach all of you a lesson.

811
00:36:56,150 --> 00:36:58,120
我眼观世界
'Cause I see everything,

812
00:36:58,140 --> 00:37:00,980
看到了两个人...
and I saw two people...

813
00:37:01,000 --> 00:37:03,250
承受着心碎之苦
with two broken hearts.

814
00:37:03,890 --> 00:37:06,410
所以你说的课是...
So the lesson was...

815
00:37:06,730 --> 00:37:09,290
是爱啊 超级少女
Love, Supergirl.

816
00:37:09,300 --> 00:37:11,260
爱的意义是...
Love is about...

817
00:37:11,280 --> 00:37:13,560
等待他人的救赎
letting yourself be saved.

818
00:37:13,730 --> 00:37:15,630
爱并不仅仅是帮助他人
It's not just about saving other people.

819
00:37:15,650 --> 00:37:17,200
虽然你们都是超级英雄
Even if you are superheroes.

820
00:37:17,230 --> 00:37:19,780
总之 非常抱歉 给你们制造了不少麻烦
Anyway, I'm sorry that I had to, like, mess with you a little bit.

821
00:37:19,810 --> 00:37:21,660
我只是想让你们进入自己的角色
I was just trying to get you to play the game,

822
00:37:21,680 --> 00:37:22,810
在音乐剧里歌唱舞蹈
do the song and dance.

823
00:37:22,840 --> 00:37:24,770
你是从另外一个...
Are you, like, from another...

824
00:37:24,790 --> 00:37:26,800
多元地球... 宇宙 来的吗
Earth-multi-verse... universe, something?

825
00:37:26,830 --> 00:37:28,520
是啊 你...
Yeah, you...

826
00:37:28,540 --> 00:37:31,050
我说了你们也不会懂的
you wouldn't even understand where I come from.

827
00:37:31,920 --> 00:37:33,210
那就这样了吗
Wait, I'm sorry, that's it?

828
00:37:33,240 --> 00:37:36,080
你就是为了给我们上一课吗
You're just gonna teach somebody else a lesson?

829
00:37:36,100 --> 00:37:37,330
对 这就是我的职责
Yeah, that's exactly what I'm gonna do

830
00:37:38,410 --> 00:37:41,110
♪ 想想你的好伙伴 ♪
♪ Think of your fellow man ♪

831
00:37:41,160 --> 00:37:43,170
♪ 帮助他渡过难关 ♪
♪ Lend him a helping hand ♪

832
00:37:43,200 --> 00:37:46,340
♪ 爱之窗 心上开一扇 ♪
♪ Put a little love in your heart ♪

833
00:38:00,800 --> 00:38:03,410
所以摆明了说
Wait, so, let me get this straight.

834
00:38:03,650 --> 00:38:06,140
你们被人摆了一道 他叫...
You got whammied by some guy named...

835
00:38:06,160 --> 00:38:07,530
音乐大师
Music Meister.

836
00:38:07,530 --> 00:38:09,260
我去 巴里 真想花钱
Damn, Barry, I'd have paid good money

837
00:38:09,290 --> 00:38:10,650
看你唱歌跳舞的样子
to see you singing and dancing.

838
00:38:10,670 --> 00:38:11,690
想的美
No.

839
00:38:11,720 --> 00:38:12,920
他不答应你
Well, he's holding out on you

840
00:38:12,940 --> 00:38:15,160
因为他唱歌好听爆了
because Barry has an amazing voice.

841
00:38:15,190 --> 00:38:16,430
-真的  -并没有
- He does! - Uh-uh.

842
00:38:16,460 --> 00:38:17,890
我真的听过他唱歌
I've actually seen him sing.

843
00:38:17,910 --> 00:38:19,000
真的吗
What? You have?

844
00:38:19,020 --> 00:38:21,220
你怎么不录个像啊
How have we not made a GIF of that?

845
00:38:21,240 --> 00:38:24,740
讲真 唱得好的可不止我一个
Well, technically, I'm not even the only one here who can sing.

846
00:38:25,050 --> 00:38:26,170
多谢夸奖 小巴
Thank you, B.A.

847
00:38:26,200 --> 00:38:27,560
什么啊 我是说卡拉
What? I was talking about Kara.

848
00:38:27,590 --> 00:38:29,590
等等... 你也会唱歌
Wait, shh... oh, you too?

849
00:38:29,620 --> 00:38:32,190
卡拉 她当然会唱了
Kara. Of course Kara can sing.

850
00:38:32,190 --> 00:38:33,720
毕竟她是超级少女
Well, her name is Supergirl.

851
00:38:33,720 --> 00:38:35,220
所以她无所不能
It's kind of implied, right?

852
00:38:35,220 --> 00:38:37,800
我们该回去了
Well, we better be getting going.

853
00:38:37,830 --> 00:38:40,340
我答应卡拉姐姐会把她安全带回去的
I promised Kara's sister we'd get her back in one piece.

854
00:38:40,370 --> 00:38:41,760
没有你们的帮助真的做不到
We couldn't have done this without you.

855
00:38:41,760 --> 00:38:43,730
-谢谢你们  -也谢谢你
- Thank you. - Thank you.

856
00:38:44,880 --> 00:38:46,260
你俩如何
How are you guys doing?

857
00:38:46,290 --> 00:38:48,050
应该没事了
Yeah, I think we'll be okay.

858
00:38:48,080 --> 00:38:49,850
可你要是再敢骗我
Although, if you lie to me again,

859
00:38:49,870 --> 00:38:51,480
我就把你压到五行山下永世不得翻身
I will drop a mountain on you.

860
00:38:51,510 --> 00:38:53,230
你是说笑吧
Wow. You mean figuratively?

861
00:38:53,260 --> 00:38:55,370
-我认真的  -好吧
- No, I mean, geologically. - Okay.

862
00:38:57,500 --> 00:38:59,080
那你们呢
What about you guys?

863
00:39:01,170 --> 00:39:02,590
再说吧
We'll see.

864
00:39:17,540 --> 00:39:20,590
我搬去西斯科家这段时间你什么都没搬啊
You didn't change anything when I moved in with Cisco.

865
00:39:20,610 --> 00:39:23,330
我不能这么做
I, um, couldn't bring myself to do it.

866
00:39:24,010 --> 00:39:26,970
过去的三年 我们经历了太多太多
You know, we've been through a lot these last three years,

867
00:39:26,980 --> 00:39:28,800
但是...
but, um...

868
00:39:29,190 --> 00:39:30,990
怎么就被困在音乐剧里了
getting stuck in a musical?

869
00:39:32,270 --> 00:39:33,630
音乐大师...
Music Meister...

870
00:39:33,660 --> 00:39:35,280
说什么剧都有可能
said that, you know, it could've been anything,

871
00:39:35,310 --> 00:39:37,840
我创造了那个世界...
that I created that world because...

872
00:39:37,860 --> 00:39:39,660
因为你是那个观众
You were watching them.

873
00:39:40,120 --> 00:39:41,710
是因为我们的爱
Because of us.

874
00:39:42,590 --> 00:39:45,260
我母亲曾说 音乐剧拥有一种
My mom used to always say that musicals have the power

875
00:39:45,260 --> 00:39:47,320
治愈一切的力量
to make everything better.

876
00:39:48,260 --> 00:39:50,270
那它有治愈你吗
Did it work?

877
00:40:05,330 --> 00:40:10,400
♪ 不知一天会如何展开 ♪
♪ Can't say how the days will unfold ♪

878
00:40:11,190 --> 00:40:16,200
♪ 不知未来会如何变化 ♪
♪ Can't change what the future may hold ♪

879
00:40:16,750 --> 00:40:19,260
♪ 但我要你与我同在 ♪
♪ But I want you in it ♪

880
00:40:19,260 --> 00:40:23,010
♪ 每一分 每一秒 ♪
♪ Every hour, every minute ♪

881
00:40:23,660 --> 00:40:26,710
♪ 这世界也许... ♪
♪ This world can race by... ♪

882
00:40:26,750 --> 00:40:29,490
♪ 节奏太快 ♪
♪ Far too fast ♪

883
00:40:29,510 --> 00:40:31,210
♪ 难以想象... ♪
♪ Hard to see... ♪

884
00:40:31,230 --> 00:40:35,420
♪ 过去的点点滴滴 ♪
♪ While it's all flying past ♪

885
00:40:36,040 --> 00:40:38,180
♪ 但现在已明了 ♪
♪ But it's clear now ♪

886
00:40:38,280 --> 00:40:42,070
♪ 当你站在我面前 ♪
♪ When you're standing here now ♪

887
00:40:42,230 --> 00:40:44,030
♪ 我注定要成为 ♪
♪ I am meant to be ♪

888
00:40:44,060 --> 00:40:48,030
♪ 永远在你身边的那个人 ♪
♪ Wherever you are next to me ♪

889
00:40:48,980 --> 00:40:53,230
♪ 我只想要 ♪
♪ All I want to do ♪

890
00:40:53,860 --> 00:40:56,720
♪ 回到你的身边 ♪
♪ Is come runnin' home to you ♪

891
00:40:56,750 --> 00:41:00,950
♪ 回到你的身边 ♪
♪ Come runnin' home to you ♪

892
00:41:00,970 --> 00:41:06,120
♪ 用我的全身心发誓 ♪
♪ And all my life, I promise to ♪

893
00:41:06,140 --> 00:41:09,210
♪ 永远伴你左右 ♪
♪ Keep runnin' home to you ♪

894
00:41:09,240 --> 00:41:14,230
♪ 永远伴你左右 ♪
♪ Keep runnin' home to you ♪

895
00:41:19,370 --> 00:41:22,460
♪ 我也能够发现 ♪
♪ And I could see it ♪

896
00:41:22,460 --> 00:41:25,490
♪ 从最开始的开始 起点的起点 ♪
♪ Right from the start, right from the start ♪

897
00:41:25,490 --> 00:41:27,960
♪ 你一直都是我 ♪
♪ That you would be ♪

898
00:41:27,960 --> 00:41:31,970
♪ 黑夜里的光亮 黑夜里的光亮 ♪
♪ Be my light in the dark, light in the dark ♪

899
00:41:31,970 --> 00:41:35,030
♪ 噢 你给我... ♪
♪ Oh, you gave me... ♪

900
00:41:35,050 --> 00:41:37,470
♪ 除了爱你外 ♪
♪ No other choice ♪

901
00:41:37,470 --> 00:41:42,440
♪ 无他的选择 ♪
♪ But to love you ♪

902
00:41:44,580 --> 00:41:49,320
♪ 我只想要 ♪
♪ All I want to do ♪

903
00:41:49,690 --> 00:41:53,020
♪ 回到你的身边 ♪
♪ Is come runnin' home to you ♪

904
00:41:53,020 --> 00:41:57,090
♪ 回到你的身边 ♪
♪ Come runnin' home to you ♪

905
00:41:57,090 --> 00:42:02,330
♪ 用我的全身心发誓 ♪
♪ And all my life I promise to ♪

906
00:42:02,550 --> 00:42:05,750
♪ 永远伴你左右 ♪
♪ Keep runnin' home to you ♪

907
00:42:05,770 --> 00:42:09,610
♪ 永远伴你 ♪
♪ Keep runnin' home ♪

908
00:42:09,710 --> 00:42:13,710
♪ 在你左右 ♪
♪ Home to you ♪

909
00:42:15,580 --> 00:42:20,960
♪ 不知一天会如何展开 ♪
♪ Can't say how the days will unfold ♪

910
00:42:21,950 --> 00:42:27,350
♪ 不知未来会如何变化 ♪
♪ Can't change what the future may hold ♪

911
00:42:28,140 --> 00:42:30,920
♪ 但我要你与我同在 ♪
♪ But I want you in it ♪

912
00:42:31,160 --> 00:42:36,000
♪ 每一分 每一秒 ♪
♪ Every hour, every minute ♪

913
00:42:39,170 --> 00:42:40,690
爱瑞斯·韦斯特
Iris West,

914
00:42:40,720 --> 00:42:42,470
你愿意嫁给我吗
will you marry me?

915
00:42:43,360 --> 00:42:44,420
我愿意
Yes.

916
00:42:45,500 --> 00:42:46,760
我愿意
Yes.
